#### Contact

648217167 (Mobile) aitorruto@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aitor-ruiz (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

PHP

HTML5

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

## Tools & Technologies

Bootstrap
Figma
Git
GitHub
JavaScript
JSON

Laravel MySQL

SQL XML

Interpersonal Skills

Teamwork
Communication

Driver's License Type B. Own vehicle

Availability
Full Time. Immediate

# Aitor Ruiz Torralbo

Web Developer

Viladecans

## Summary

My name is Aitor Ruiz Torralbo, I am a web developer from Viladecans, Barcelona, Spain born on March 14, 2001. I have finished the upper cycle of web application development. My native languages are Spanish and Catalan and I have a lot of experience with English. My goal is to improve my level and knowledge to create my own company in the future.

# Experience

Soluciones web - Nivel Z Web developer technician November 2020 - April 2021 (6 months) Viladecans, Cataluña, España

Web page design. SEO web positioning. Google Adwords SEM. Online marketing. On-line projects. Hosting.

Viladecans Town Hall Computer Technical Specialist November 2018 - April 2019 (6 months) Viladecans, Cataluña, España

Hardware and software installation and repair. Network maintenance. Troubleshooting.

## Education

#### **CEFP Núria**

Superior Technician in Web Application Development, Information Technology · (September 2019 - July 2021)

## INS Torre Roja

Half cycle microcomputer systems and networks, Technology / Computer Hardware Technician · (September 2018 - July 2020)